is something like a touchdown in our city
like a fade right into the black
like a
if i disappear
or anybody knows the song sounds
i can feel you like a
it's like you
follow me everywhere
i go call me crazy or insane
all i know is
i feel too close to control
so i gotta get
i can see you standing in the land with his arms
and it took you five hours
that could
on the around the
i think i see this
i can see you still like
he's just your understudy
like you get to know
second
third and
i see
can i do let me tell me i'm not your problem
i don't know it's not wrong
i'm an exi
i think you see this for so long
you not side
so step
there is no way to
say i get it back
cause we don't
it's so funny that you
that i wish
my name is the place that i can escape you
ghost
don't tell me
i'll be here at the end
i got a friend
oh
and will go
but everything reminds me when it comes
when you left the shoulder
should tell you to teach me
tell me a constantly moving on these days
covering everything that i need
my friends and i can't escape you
i think i
now you
oh
we can say goodnight
though
while my words
are white
my life
it's not the same as it
what are you
what kind of things do you want
this is not your love is
so we just want to love
it's not the same
i don't know how you live
in the hills gives me chills
say of angel
if you ever make me
i'll be the first one
i don't say a
you want
i gotta get going with my life
'cause everything's hurts you by a ghost now
i think that this goes down
ever since you left
that went coast so alone
i've been so
ever since you left
i've been low on the low
yeah
i can't help but all the nights we wasted together
till you feel strange
like the weather
you got our heart so cold
like a summer
your bad ex is calling me one way
flight to all my dreams
baby
if not with the world
i'ma try myself
crazy in love
have this ghost town
i gotta move
going with my life
'cause everything's haunted
are you ghost
now i gotta move on
i'm sick of this ghost
now i gotta get
i gotta get going with my life
you see this
sometimes i feel something like a touchdown in our city
like a fade
right into the black
like a gold
if i disappeared with anybody else
and sometimes i could feel you like a like
you follow me everywhere
i go call me crazy or insane
all i know is
i feel you're too close to let it go
so i gotta get
i gotta get going with my life
you thing's
i see